Guide to the Alfred Stieglitz / Georgia O'Keeffe Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alfred Stieglitz: Correspondence, 1874-1950; Series I; 40.4; (97 boxes)
  - PERSONAL AND BUSINESS CORRESPONDENCE
    - Dove, Arthur, 1914-32 (Box 13, Folder 316-327)
      Folder 319 includes: poems by Holly Raleigh
      Folder 320 includes: letter from Dove to Mr. Phillips
      Folder 326 includes: letter from Talens of Talens & Zoon
    - Dove, Arthur, 1933-40 (Box 14, Folder 328-338)
      Folder 330 includes: letter from Holger Cahill on behalf of the First Municipal Art Exhibition
      Folder 334 includes: typescript copy of letter from Sherwood Anderson
    - Dove, Arthur, 1941-46, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 339-343)
      See also: Living American Art, Box 31, folder 733
      See also: Phillips Memorial Gallery (1927, 1934), Box 38, folders 912-918
    - Dove, Arthur: excerpts from letters, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 344)
    - Dove, Arthur: letter to Bill, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 345)
    - Dove, Arthur: letters to and from Arthur J. Eddy, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 346)
    - Dove, Arthur: letter to John Marin, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - Dove, Helen Torr
      See: Helen Torr, Box 49, folder 1177
    - Dove, William; Dove, Marian, 1936-42 (Box 15, Folder 348)
    - Downtown Gallery
      See: Arthur Dove (1934 Mar), Boxes 13-15, folders 316-343
    - Drake, A. W.
    - Dreier, Katherine S., 1917-31 (Box 15, Folder 349)
    - Dreiser, Theodore, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 350)
    - Dresdener Gesellschaft zur Förderung der Amateur-Photographie
      See: Internationale Photographische Austellung, Dresden, Box 25, folder 598
    - Droth, Andrew, 1934-45 (Box 15, Folder 351)
    - Dubreuil, Pierre Marcel, 1906-12 (Box 15, Folder 352)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1920-36, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 353)
    - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, Inc., 1939-40 (Box 15, Folder 354)
    - Dugmore, Arthur Radclyffe, 1912-13, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 355)
    - DuMond, Frank V.
      See: Lewis and Clark Centennial Exposition, Box 31, folder 715
    - Duncan, Charles, 1916-32, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 356)
    - Duveen, Joseph, 1926, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 357)
    - Dyer, William B., 1899-1907, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 358-359)
      See also: Joseph Keiley (1900 Jun), Box 27, folders 635-644
    - "E" general, 1907-44, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 360)
    - E. Steiger & Company, 1911-17 (Box 16, Folder 361)
    - E. Weyhe, 1924-31, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 362)
    - Eastman, George
      See: Eastman Kodak Company, Box 16, folder 363-364
    - Eastman Kodak Company, 1898-1933 (Box 16, Folder 363-364)
      See also: Katharine Rhoades (1915 Oct), Box 40, folder 970-978
    - Eastman Kodak Company, Folmer and Schwing Division, 1906-17 (Box 16, Folder 365)
    - Eckstein, Florence
      See: Selma Stieglitz Schubart, Box 55, folders 1328-1329
    - Eckstein, W. E., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 366)
    - Eddy, Arthur Jerome, 1913-20 (Box 16, Folder 367)
    - Edelson, Rebecca, 1915-16, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 368)
    - Ederheimer, Richard, 1921-22 (Box 16, Folder 369)
    - Edson, Winona Charlier, 1928, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 370)
    - Eerste Internationale Salon van Kunstfotografie, Hague
      See: Daguerre Photoclub, Box 11, folder 275
    - L'Effort [Cercle d'Art Photographique], Brussels, 1903-06 (Box 16, Folder 371)
    - Eggers, George William
      See: Worcester Art Museum, Box 52, folder 1273
    - Eglington, Guy C., 1922, 1924, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 372)
      See also: The International Studio, Box 25, folder 596
    - Ehrenfest, Paul, 1924-32 (Box 16, Folder 373)
      See also: Edna Clare Bryner, Box 8, folder 191
    - Ehrman, Laura, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 374)
    - Eickemeyer, Rudolf, 1894 Dec (Box 16, Folder 375)
    - Eickemeyer, Rudolf, Jr., 1894-1903 (Box 16, Folder 376)
    - Eilshemius, Louis Michel, 1923-40, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 377-378)
    - Eilshemius, Louis Michel: mailing to Marsden Hartley, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 379)
    - Einstein, R. E., 1936-40 (Box 16, Folder 380)
    - Einstein, William, 1932-37 (Box 16, Folder 381-383)
      See also: Museum of Modern Art (1936), Box 36, folder 847-848
    - Einstein, William, 1938-46 (Box 17, Folder 384-392)
    - Einstein, William: letter to Dallas Museum of Art, 1936 Sep 7 (Box 17, Folder 393)
    - Einstein, William: letters to Arthur Dove, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 394)
    - Emanuel, Charles, 1907-09 (Box 17, Folder 395)
    - Emerson, Peter Henry, 1888-1914 (Box 17, Folder 396)
      Note: includes transcriptions of letters made by Nancy Newhall
      See also: Thomas Bedding, Box, 4, folder 99
    - Emerson, Peter Henry, 1924-33 (Box 17, Folder 397)
    - Emmerich, Heinrich, 1907, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 398)
    - Encke, Fedor, 1912 Nov 11 (Box 17, Folder 399)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica
      See: Edward Weston, Box 51, folders 1234-1235
    - Enters, Angna: correspondence, 1926-44, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 400-401)
    - Enters, Angna: holiday cards, 1927-45, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 402)
    - Epstein, [Jacob Hermann ?]: letter to Emmeline Stieglitz, 1915 May 12 (Box 18, Folder 403)
    - Esposizione Internazionale d'Arte Decorativa Moderna, Turin, 1902-03 (Box 18, Folder 404)
    - Estorick, Eric, 1934, [1937?], n.d. (Box 18, Folder 405)
    - Eugene, Frank: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 406)
    - Eugene, Frank: correspondence, 1899-1927 (Box 18, Folder 407-409)
      See also: Camera-Klub, Wien, Box 8, folder 205
      See also: F. Bruckmann K.G. (1913), Box 19, folders 420-423
      See also: Francis Bruguière (1913), Box 8, folder 187
      See also: L. von Glasersfeld, Box 21, folder 483
      See also: John Nilsen Laurvik (1913), Box 30, folder 701
      See also: Friedrich Raab (1907, 1913, 1915), Box 39, folders 953-955
      See also: Edward Steichen (1920), Box 46, folders 1091-1097
    - Eugene, Frank: letters to Emmeline and Katherine Stieglitz, 1904-09 (Box 18, Folder 410)
    - Evans, Bob, 1940-41 (Box 18, Folder 411)
    - Evans, Frederick H.: correspondence, 1902-15 (Box 18, Folder 412-413)
      See also: Albright Art Gallery (1911), Box 1, folder 17-18
      See also: R. Child Bayley (1908), Box 4, folders 86-90
      See also: Joseph Keiley (1906, 1909), Box 27, folders 635-644
      See also: Heinrich Kühn (1905 Mar), Box 29, folder 676-686
      See also: John Nilsen Laurvik, Box 30, folder 701
    - Evans, Frederick H.: exhibition notes and lists, 1905, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 414)
    - Evans, Frederick H.: letters to Edward Steichen, 1902-03 (Box 18, Folder 415)
    - Evening Sun, 1911, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 416)
    - Exposition Universelle Internationale de 1900 Paris, France, International Congress of Photographers (Box 18, Folder 417)
      See also: Eastman Kodak Company (1900), Box 16, folders 363-364
    - Ezekiel, Henry Clay, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 418)
    - "F" general, 1898-1946, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 419)
    - F. Bruckmann K.G., 1907-20 (Box 19, Folder 420-423)
    - F. Bruckmann K.G.: letters to Edward Steichen and Paul Haviland, 1910 Sep 19 (Box 19, Folder 424)
    - Faggi, Alfeo, 1922-23, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 425)
    - Farnsworth, E. J., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 426)
    - Fénéon, Félix
      See: Bernheim Jeune & Cie, Box 4, folder 112
    - Ferguson, Eugene Lee, 1897-99 (Box 19, Folder 427)
      See also: Camera Club of the C. Bi. C., Box 9, folder 203
    - Ferriss, Hugh
      See: Architectural League of New York, Box 3, folder 53
    - Fesler, Caroline, 1944-45 (Box 19, Folder 428)
    - Field, Hamilton Easter, 1911-21 (Box 19, Folder 429)
    - Field, William B. Osgood, 1910-17 (Box 19, Folder 430)
    - First School of American Dada, 1937 Oct 25 (Box 19, Folder 431)
    - Fischel, Marguerite K.; Fischel, Ellis, 1929-43 (Box 19, Folder 432)
    - Fisher, Grace Norcross, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 433)
    - Fisher, William Murrell
      See: William Murrell, Box 36, folder 842
    - Fleisher, Maurice
    - Fleischman, Helen Krator; Fleischman, Leon S., 1915-24, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 434)
    - Fleming, Asta, 1924-34, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 435)
    - Flint, Ralph, 1930-36, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 436)
    - Florsheim, Claire, 1934, 1936, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 437)
    - Fogg Art Museum, 1928-31 (Box 19, Folder 438)
    - Folmer and Schwing Company
      See: Eastman Kodak Company, Box 16, folders 363-364
    - Foord, John; Foord, Andrew, 1890-1926 (Box 19, Folder 439)
    - Forbes, Edward Waldo
      See: Fogg Art Museum, Box 19, folder 438
    - Force, Juliana
      See: Whitney Museum of American Art, Box 52, folder 1253
    - The Forum, 1925, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 440)
    - Fox, Douglas C.
      See: Baltimore Museum of Art, Box, 3, folder 78
    - Fox, William Henry
      See: Brooklyn Museum, Box 8, folder 180
    - Frank, Alma Magoon, 1930-39, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 441)
    - Frank, Margaret Naumberg, 1919-23. n.d. (Box 19, Folder 442)
    - Frank, Peggy
      See: Cincinnati Modern Art Society, Box 9, folder 228
    - Frank Seaman Incorporated, 1911-15 (Box 19, Folder 443)
      See also: Bausch and Lomb, Box 4, folder 85
    - Frank, Waldo David: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 444)
    - Frank, Waldo David: correspondence, 1916-20 (Box 19, Folder 445)
    - Frank, Waldo David: correspondence, 1921-44, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 446-450)
      See also: Edward Dahlberg (1939), Box 11, folder 276
      See also: Alma Magoon Frank, Box 19, folder 441
    - Fraprie, Frank Roy, 1907-11 (Box 20, Folder 451)
      See also: American Photography, Box 1, folder 33
      See also: Boston Camera Club, Box 5, folder 125
      See also: Heinrich Kühn (1909), Box 29, folders 676-686
    - Fraser, Joseph T.
      See: Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, Box 38, folder 910
    - Fraudsen, Islem
      See: Dorothy Sloane, Box 45, folder 1073
    - The Freeman
      See: Van Wyck Brooks, Box 8, folder 183
    - Freeman, Helen, 1922-25, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 452)
    - Freer, Charles Lang, 1910, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 453)
    - French, Herbert Greer, 1904-14, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 454)
    - French, Joseph Lewis, 1914, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 455)
    - French, Wilfred A.
    - Friday Morning Club (Los Angeles)
      See: Macdonald-Wright, Stanton: correspondence (1920), box 33
    - Frohne, E.
    - Frueh, Alfred J., 1912-13 (Box 20, Folder 456)
    - Frye, Mary Hamilton, 1915 May 2 (Box 20, Folder 457)
    - Fuguet, Dallett, 1899-1920, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 458)
    - Fuguet, Dallett: letter to Paul Haviland, 1909 Sep 30 (Box 20, Folder 459)
    - Fuguet, Dallett: letter to Joseph Keiley, 1909 Aug 19 (Box 20, Folder 460)
    - Fulton, Mrs. John, 1939 Jun 7 (Box 20, Folder 461)
    - Funston, Nancy, 1935, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 462)
    - Furman, E. H.
    - "G" general, 1902-46, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 463)
    - Gable, William F.; Gable, Robert B., 1914-15 (Box 20, Folder 464)
    - Gable, William F.: bookplates, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 465)
    - Gag, Wanda, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 466)
    - Gaisman, Henry J., 1914-26 (Box 20, Folder 467)
    - Galerie Druet, 1911 Jun 24 (Box 20, Folder 468)
    - Galerie Miethke Ausstellung von Werkenalter und Moderner Kunst, 1909, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 469)
    - Gallatin, Albert Eugene, 1921-27, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 470)
    - Galsworthy, John, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 471)
    - Gannett, Lewis, 1933-34 (Box 20, Folder 472)
      See also: The Nation, Box 36, folder 853
    - Garfield, George and Frances O'Brien, 1926-31 (Box 20, Folder 473)
    - Garland, Marie Tudor, 1930, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 474)
    - Garo, John H., 1912 (Box 20, Folder 475)
      See also: Photographers' Association of New England, Box 39, folder 922
    - Gast, John, 1890-91, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 476)
    - Geiger, Willi, 1907-12, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 477)
      See also: Raab family, Box 39, folder 957
    - Gellerman, Henry
      See: De Hirsh Margules (1945), Box 33, folders 772-775
    - Gellert, Hugo
      See: Artists' Committee of Action for the Municipal Art Gallery and Center, Box 3, folder 61
    - Genthe, Arnold, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 478)
    - George F. Of, Inc., 1911-27, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 479)
      See also: George Ferdinand Of, Box 21, folder 479
    - George R. Read and Company, 1912-17 (Box 21, Folder 480)
    - Gesellschaft zur Förderung der Amateur-Photographie Hamburg, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 481)
      See also: Ernst Juhl, Box 26, folder 622
    - Gilder, R. W.
    - Glaser, Curt, 1932, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 482)
    - Glasersfeld, L. von, 1911-12, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 483)
      See also: Frank Eugene (1908), Box 18, folders 407-409
    - Glasgow International Exhibition, 1902 Jan 9 (Box 21, Folder 484)
    - Gledhill, W. Edwin, 1914, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 485)
    - Goepfert, Louise
      See: Louise Goepfert March, Box 33, folder 770
    - Goerke, Franz, 1896-1910, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 486)
    - Goetz, Fritz, 1921-27, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 487)
      See also: Friedrich Raab (1907), Box 39, folders 953-955
    - Golden Gate International Exhibition, 1939 Jan 11 (Box 21, Folder 488)
    - Goldman, Emma, 1912-17 (Box 21, Folder 489)
      See also: David Liebovitz (1927 Aug), Box 31, folder 721
    - Goll, Claire, 1940-41 (Box 21, Folder 490)
      See also: Luise Rainer, Box 40, folder 958
    - Gollomb, Joseph, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 491)
    - Goloboff, Alice Holtman, 1939-43 (Box 21, Folder 492)
    - Goodwin, Philip L., 1921-45 (Box 21, Folder 493)
    - Goodwin, Walter L., Jr., 1934 Sep 8 (Box 21, Folder 494)
      See also: J. B. Lippincott, Box 25, folder 601
    - Goodyear, A. Conger
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1941 Apr 30 (Box 21, Folder 495)
    - Gotshall, J. W., 1917 (Box 21, Folder 496)
    - Gould, Wallace, 1922, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 497)
    - Graeme and Company, 1910-13 (Box 21, Folder 498)
    - Grand Central Art Galleries, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 499)
    - Greene, Balcomb, 1933 Nov 1 (Box 21, Folder 500)
    - Greene, Belle daCosta, 1909-22, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 501)
    - Greene, Felix, 1941, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 502)
    - Greenwich Village
      See: Guido Bruno, Box 8, folder 188
    - Gregg, Frederick James, 1911-15 (Box 21, Folder 503)
    - Griffith, O. L., 1916-17, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 504)
    - Grolman, Adolf von
      See: Internationale Ausstellung Künstlerischer Porträt-Photographieen, Wiesbaden (1903), Box 25, folder 597
    - Grosse Kunstausstellung Dresden, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 505)
    - Grosse Kunstausstellung Dresden: letter to Frank Eugene, 1904 Sep 3 (Box 21, Folder 506)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1934-41 (Box 21, Folder 507)
    - Guild of Allied Arts, Buffalo, 1916-17, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 508)
    - Guillaume, Paul, 1914-15 (Box 21, Folder 509)
    - Guteman, Ernest, 1929-40 (Box 21, Folder 510)
    - "H" general, 1900-46, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 511-512)
    - Hall, Clifton Rumery, 1933-39 (Box 21, Folder 513)
    - Hallowell, Robert, 1924-26 (Box 21, Folder 514)
    - Halpert, Samuel, 1912-14 (Box 21, Folder 515)
    - Hanna, Forman G., 1911, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 516)
    - Hanna, Leonard C., Jr., 1927-28 (Box 21, Folder 517)
    - Hapgood, Hutchins, 1912-44, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 518-519)
    - Hapgood, Neith Boyce, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 520)
    - Harcourt, Brace & Company, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 521)
    - Hare, Elizabeth Sage, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 522)
    - Harshe, Robert B.
      See: Art Institute of Chicago, Box 3, folder 60
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1911-23 (Box 22, Folder 523-535)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1924-42 (Box 23, Folder 536-541)
      See also: Lillian Baer, Box 3, folder 73
    - Hartley, Marsden: letters to Emmeline Stieglitz, 1912-13 (Box 23, Folder 542)
    - Hartley, Marsden: letters to American Express and Bartz & Company, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 543)
    - Hartman, Bertram, 1931-44, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 544)
    - Hartman, Gusta
    - Hartmann, Sadakichi; Hartmann, Betty W., 1899-1942, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 545-546)
      See also: Joseph Keiley (1904 Aug), Box 27, folders 635-644
    - Hartmann, Sadakichi: letters to Eugene Meyer, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 547)
    - Harvard Society of Contemporary Art
      See: Benjamin Kopman, Box 28, folder 671
    - Harvey, Dorothy Dudley, 1922-33 (Box 23, Folder 548)
    - Hasemann, Wilhelm, 1904, 1907 (Box 23, Folder 549)
    - Hasemann, Luise, 1923
    - Hastings, Charles
      See: The Amateur Photographer, Box 2, folder 26
    - Havel, Hippolyte, 1914-15 (Box 23, Folder 550)
    - Haviland, Julia D., 1909 Feb 15 (Box 24, Folder 551)
    - Haviland, Frank Burty; Haviland, William, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 552)
    - Haviland, Paul, 1908-38 (Box 24, Folder 553-554)
    - Haviland, Paul: Christmas cards by Allen Lewis, 1910, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 555)
      See also: Box 156, folder 2888
    - Haviland, Paul: letters to and from Clarence White, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 556)
    - Haviland, Paul: letters to and from Yale University Press, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 557)
    - Haviland, Paul: postcard to Marius de Zayas, 1915 Aug 18 (Box 24, Folder 558)
    - Hayes, Bartlett H.
      See: Addison Gallery of American Art, Box 1, folder 15
    - Ház, Nicholas, 1933-37, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 559)
    - Hearn, Charles W.
      See: Photographers' Association of New England, Box 39, folder 922
    - Hechenbleikner, Christl and Louis, 1939-45, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 560)
    - Hecht, Zoltan
      See: Artists' Committee of Action for the Municipal Art Gallery, Box 3, folder 61
    - Heliochrome Engraving Company
      See: John Foord, Box 19, folder 439
      See: John Gast, Box 20, folder 476
    - Hellman, George Sidney
      See: Cyril Kay-Scott, Box 26, folder 630
    - Henderson, Archibald, 1905-12 (Box 24, Folder 561)
    - Henderson, Helen Weston, 1912-15 (Box 24, Folder 562)
    - Henderson, Hunt, 1928-32 (Box 24, Folder 563)
    - Henle, Fritz
      See: Eliot Porter, Box 39, folder 938
    - Henneberg, Hugo
    - Henri [dancer], 1923-29 (Box 24, Folder 564)
    - Herald, Leon Serabian, 1929-30 (Box 24, Folder 565)
    - Herbert and Huesgen Company, 1911-17 (Box 24, Folder 566)
    - Herrmann, Eva, 1926-42, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 567)
      Includes: letter to Leo Stieglitz
      See also: Frank Herrmann, Box 24, folder 568
    - Herrmann, Frank Simon ("Sime"), 1881-1938, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 568)
    - Hess-Ives Corporation
      See: O. L. Griffith, Box 21, folder 504
    - Hewitt, Arthur, 1901, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 569)
    - Heymel, Alfred Walter, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 570)
    - Hine, Lewis Wickes, 1906 Dec 14 (Box 24, Folder 571)
    - Hinton, Alfred Horsley: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 572)
    - Hinton, Alfred Horsley: correspondence, 1896-1907 (Box 24, Folder 573-576)
      See also: Heinrich Kühn (1904), Box 29, folders 676-686
    - Hirsch, Stefan, 1922, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 577)
    - Hirst, Harriet E., 1935, 1941, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 578)
    - Hodges, F. B., 1915 (Box 24, Folder 579)
    - Hoeber, Arthur, 1902-14 (Box 25, Folder 580)
    - Hofmann, Julius
    - Hoffman, Burton C.
      See: Knight Publications, Box 28, folder 664
    - Hoffman, Malvina, 1939 Apr 8 (Box 25, Folder 581)
    - Hofmeister, Theodor and Oskar, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 582)
      See also: Gesellschaft zur Förderung der Amateur-Photographie, Box 21, folder 481
    - Holland, Clive
      See: The Studio, Box 49, folder 1152
    - Holme, Charles
    - Hope, Henry Radford
      See: Indiana University, Box 25, folder 594
    - Hopfmiller, A. M.
      See: Shadowland, Box 45, folder 1061
    - Hoppé, Emil Otto, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 583)
      See also: Frank Eugene (1910), Box 18, folders 407-409
    - Hord, Spencer B.
      See: Rubincam, Harry C., Box 42, folder 1014
    - Hornor, S. Stockton, 1903-04 (Box 25, Folder 584)
    - Horter, Earl, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 585)
    - Howald, Ferdinand, 1925-26 (Box 25, Folder 586)
    - Howard, Evelyn, 1932-37 (Box 25, Folder 587)
    - Howe, Alice M.
      See: Katharine N. Rhoades (1930), Box 40, folders 970-978
    - Howe, George, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 588)
    - Hoyt, Jerome
      See: John Weichsel, Box 51, folder 1228
    - Hubbard, Elbert, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 589)
    - Huebsch, Benjamin W., 1923-32 (Box 25, Folder 590)
    - Hutson, Victoria Ebbels, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 591)
    - Huxley, Aldous
      See: Dorothy Brett (1931 Apr), Box 7, folders 156-162
    - "I" general, 1911-44, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 592)
    - Iklé, Charles F., 1915-25 (Box 25, Folder 593)
    - Indiana University, Fine Arts Department, 1944, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 594)
    - International Art Center
      See: Arthur Dove (1935), Boxes 13-15, folders 316-343
    - International Composers' Guild
      See: Edgar Varèse, Box 50, folder 1201
    - International Linked Ring
      See: George Davison (1904), Box 11, folders 283-285
    - The International News Company, 1915-17 (Box 25, Folder 595)
    - International Photographic Society
    - International Society of Pictorial
      Photographers
    - The International Studio, 1907-21 (Box 25, Folder 596)
      See also: Herbert Seligmann (1921), Boxes 44-45, folders 1044-1056
    - Internationale Ausstellung künstlerischer Porträt-Photographieen, Wiesbaden (1903), 1902-04 (Box 25, Folder 597)
    - Internationale Photographische Austellung, Berlin (1904-05)
      See: Franz Goerke, Box 21, folder 486
    - Internationale Photographische Austellung, Budapest (1910)
      See: Heinrich Kühn, Box 29, folders 676-686
    - Internationale Photographische Ausstellung, Dresden, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 598)
      See also: Frank Roy Fraprie, Box 20, folder 451
      See also: Heinrich Kühn (1908-9), Box 29, folders 676-686
    - Iselin, O'Donnell, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 599)
    - Ivins, William M.
    - "J" general, 1910-44, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 600)
    - J. B. Lippincott Company, 1932-33 (Box 25, Folder 601)
    - J. J. Waddington, Ltd., 1903 (Box 25, Folder 602)
    - J. L. Lewis, 1911-12 (Box 25, Folder 603)
    - J. W. Masters and Company, 1911-16 (Box 25, Folder 604)
    - Jack, Theodore
      See: Randolph-Macon Woman's College, Box 40, folder 960
    - Jacob, C. Max, 1915-16 (Box 25, Folder 605)
    - Jahrbuch für Kunstphotographie und Internationale Kunstphotographien
      See: Ernst Juhl, Box 26, folder 622
    - James, Oliver B., 1938-44 (Box 25, Folder 606)
    - James, Rebecca Salsbury Strand, 1921-25 (Box 25, Folder 607-611)
      See also: Paul Strand (1924), Box 48, folders 1129-1145
    - James, Rebecca Salsbury Strand, 1926-46, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 612-614)
    - James, William F., 1900-03, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 615)
    - Jerome, Jerome K.
      See: Alvin Langdon Coburn (1904), Box 10, folders 236-240
    - Jessen, Peter
      See: Koniglichen Kunstgewerbe-Museums, Box 28, folder 669
    - Jewell, Edward Alden
      See: The New York Times, Box 36, folder 866
    - John Lane Company
      See: The International Studio, Box 25, folder 596
    - John Wanamaker, 1912-21, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 616)
    - John Weber Estate, 1911-12 (Box 26, Folder 617)
    - Johnson, Alvin
      See: New School for Social Research, Box 36, folder 859
    - Johnson, Ellen
      See: Allen Memorial Art Museum, Box 1, folder 24
    - Johnson, Robert Wood, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 618)
    - Johnson, Walter Willard ("Spud"), 1929 (Box 26, Folder 619)
    - Johnston, Frances Benjamin, 1896-1908, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 620)
    - Johnston, J. Dudley, 1910-37 (Box 26, Folder 621)
    - Jones, Lewis B.
    - Josephson, Matthew
      See: Broom, Box 8, folder 184
    - Juhl, Ernst, 1896-1912 (Box 26, Folder 622)
    - "K" general, 1899-1946, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 623)
    - Kahn, George, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 624)
    - Kalonyme, Louis, 1926-45, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 625)
    - Kanaga, Consuelo, 1923-27 (Box 26, Folder 626)
      See also: Donald Litchfield (1924 Jun), Box 31, folders 725-730
    - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1913, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 627)
    - Karfiol, Bernard, 1923-28 (Box 26, Folder 628)
    - Kasebier, Gertrude, 1899-1914, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 629)
      See also: Edward Steichen (1901), Box 46, folders 1091-1097
    - Kay-Scott, Cyril, 1921-34, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 630)